ILGWU. David Melman papers, 5780/152
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Rio and Calvin Klein Jeans Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Calvin Klein New York City Sampleroom, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Calvin Klein Original Signed Agreements, 1991-1994 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Calvin Klein Swimwear, 1989-1990 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Calvin Klein Draft of License Agreement with "S", 1999 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement [folder 1 of 2], 1994-1997 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement [folder 2 of 2], 1994-1997 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Calvin Klein Master Agreement Correspondence, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Calvin Klein New York City Sampleroom [additional], 1994 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Calvin Klein New York City Sampleroom, 1994-1997 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Calvin Klein Secaucus, NJ Negotiations, 1995-1996 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Calvin Klein Original Signed Agreements, 1994-1997 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Calvin Klein Contractors, 1994-1995 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Calvin Klein Contract Termination Notices and Correspondence, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Calvin Klein Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- Calvin Klein Cosmetics Warehouse (Box 71, Folder 19)
- Calvin Klein Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- United States Bankruptcy Court. Bidermann Industries [folder 1 of 2], 1995 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- United States Bankruptcy Court. Bidermann Industries [folder 2 of 2], 1995 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Otterbourg, Steindler, Houston and Rosen, P.C., 1996 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Bidermann Industries Bankruptcy, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Bidermann Industries Bankruptcy, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Bidermann Industries, Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1995-1996 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Bidermann Industries, Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1995-1996 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Plaid Clothing Group Bankruptcy, 1995-1997 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Court Materials [folder 1 of 2], 1995-1997 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Court Materials [folder 2 of 2], 1995-1997 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Credit Agreement, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Report to the Creditor's Committee, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Official Committee of Unsecured Creditors of Bidermann Industries [folder 1 of 2], 1996 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Official Committee of Unsecured Creditors of Bidermann Industries [folder 2 of 2], 1996 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Bidermann Industries 1996 Fiscal Year Budget, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Triangle Fire Survivors, 1984-1991 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Triangle Fire 75th Anniversary. Financial Data, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Triangle Fire 75th Anniversary. Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Triangle Fire Rally, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Union Health Center, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Union Health Center 75th Anniversary, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Triangle Fire Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Triangle Fire Rally, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Triangle Fire Rally, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Industry Agreements, 1985-1988 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Reviewing Northeast Region Contracts, 1985-1989 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- NAFTA Grassroots Committee, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- NAFTA, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- New York State Legislation, 1994-1996 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- New York Times Health Insurance Articles, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Local 153, 1988-1994 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Delegate Credentials. AFL-CIO Convention, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- AFL Convention, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Campaign for Justice, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- Career and Education Expo, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- President Bill Clinton, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 22)
- Homework Hearing Videotape Correspondence, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 23)
- Homework Non-ILG Publications, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 24)
- Homework. Letters to Department of Labor, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 26)
- Chinese Videotapes, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Industrial Union Department 1988 Convention (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Labor Management Committee, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Flexible Manufacturing Systems Report, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Labor Management Committees, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Industrial Union Department Convention, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Homework Committee, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 7)